Arts and Sciences, College of; Records ua600
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- College of Arts and Sciences, 1955-1995; 2; 18.4 cubic ft.
  - Administrative Organization, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Basic Sheet, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - General, 1966 November 11 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Chairmen, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Council of Economic Edu, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Chairmen, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Summer School, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Chairmen, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Chairman, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Meadows Paul, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Staffing, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Chairmen, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Committee on Soc. Studies, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Research Plans for Organization of 1967 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Enrollment Projections, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Seminars, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Four School Study, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Meetings of Deans of Schools and Colleges with Kuusisto, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Sabbaticals, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Miwa Paul, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Fiser Correspondence, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Kuusisto Allan, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence and General Information, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence and General Information, 1965; 1966 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Opening Day, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - General, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1968; 1969 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Deans and Probation Lists, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Pre-registration, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Visitors, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Roundtable Seminars, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Short Curses Work Shops Conferences, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - University of the Air, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, 1966; 1967; 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Committee on Continuing Education, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Nebraska Center For Continuing Education, 1963-1967 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Ada Craig Walker Award, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Advanced Placement Program, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Renumbering Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Committee For Undergraduate Admissions, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - General, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Graduate Studies, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - General, 1966; 1967 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Indonesian Program, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - John Slocum, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Report, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Publicity, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Report Comments on the Report, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Agenda, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - General, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Advancement Statistics, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Advisement Academic, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Dismissals, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Enrollments, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Warnings, 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence, General, 1966; 1967 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Statistics, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Budget, 1967-1968; 1969 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Seymour William, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Registration, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Budget, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - General, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Schedules, 1965; 1966 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Art, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Astronomy, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Biology, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Chemistry, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Classics, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Comparative Literature, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - English, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - Earth Sciences, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Economics, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - General Sciences, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - Geography, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - Germanic Slavic Languages and Literature, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - History, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Inter-American Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Romance Languages and Literature, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Mathematics, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Music, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Philosophy, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - Physics, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Political Science, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Psychology, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - Sociology and Anthropology, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - Speech and Dramatic Art, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Ancillary Services Director of Brewer, 1966; 1967; 1968; 1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Data on Education, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - NDEA Education Funds, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Joint Awards Council, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - NDEA Fellowships, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Scholar Fellow, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Classroom Space, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Olsen, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Calendar School Year, 1967-1968; 1969 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Examination Schedule, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Man Agreement Position Designation, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Space Allocation, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Space Planning, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Administrative Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Budget, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Business General, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1967; 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Enrollment Report Statistics, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Instructors, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Overdue Grades, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Space Planning, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence General Olsen, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Restructuring, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Division of Humanities, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Humanistic Studies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Art, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Dr. of Arts Program, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Art History, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Classics, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Comparative Literature, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - English, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - French, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - German, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Hispanic and Italian Studies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Music, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Philosophy, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Rhetoric and Communication, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Russian and Slavic Languages, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Theatre, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Interdisciplinary Studies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Division of Social and Behavioral, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - African and Afro- Americans Studies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Anthropology, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Economics, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Environmental Studies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Geography, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - History, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - History Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Psychology, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Puerto Rican Studies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Sociology, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Inter-American Studies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Interdisciplinary Studies Asian, Environmental, Russian, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Division of Science and Mathematics, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Astronomy, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Atmospheric Science, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - ASRC, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Biology, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Chemistry, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Computer Science, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Geology, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Judaic Studies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Mathematics, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Physics, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - SUNYA Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - SUNYA Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - SUNYA Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts Fiver year plan Executive Summary, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - College Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - College of Social and Behavioral Sciences Salary Listings by Department, 1982-1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Social and Behavioral Sciences Faculty Lines by Department, 1982-1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Departmental Discretionary Pay Increase Charts, 1979-1985 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "Budget Proposal 1994-1995" (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "W.D. Means Contribution to 10/31/95 Meeting of Voting Faculty of CAS", 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Self-Studies and Middle States Accreditation, 1968-1971; 3; 1 cubic ft.
  This series documents materials prepared for the University's accreditation by the Middle States Commission on Higher Education. These materials represent the Humanities Division's preparations for the accreditation process and include departmental reports, correspondence and memoranda, forms, self-studies by academic departments and articles circulated by members of the Humanities Division's committee charged with overseeing preparations for the accreditation.
  Materials in this series appear to have been previously processed and foldered. They have been retained in the order they were found in.
  - General Notes Interviews, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Preparation, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Purposes, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Humanities, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Humanities in Depth, 1971 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Humanities in Depth, 1970 March; 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Vassar College, 1968; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Distribution, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Humanities Report, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Resources, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Faculty, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Distributed documents, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Academic Program and Grievance, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Drafts, Documents, Agendas Statistics, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Notes, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Accreditation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Accreditations Report, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Accreditations, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Accreditations Report, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Accreditations Report Rberts, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Accreditations Awins, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Humanities in Depth, 1970 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Humanities Draft Report Self Study, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - HUMID, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Department Questionaries, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Department Questionaries, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Performing Arts, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1965-2011; 4; 10.33 cubic ft.
  This series documents the administration of the College of Humanities and Fine Arts, particularly between the college's founding in 1978 and 1993. Series contains correspondence, program and center proposals, committee meeting minutes, Three- and Five-Year Plans, VHS tapes of events of the College's China Institute, Capital District Humanities Project reports, faculty activity forms, annual reports.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Series contains VHS tapes.
  - NEH Proposal, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - NEH Proposal, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - NEH Proposal, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Appendices, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Appendices, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Appendices, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Gregory I. Stevens, ca. 1978; 1973-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Narrative Report, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Narrative Report, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bibliography Comparative Literature, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Selected Programs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - A Learning Odyssey Program Proposal, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - A Learning Odyssey Program Proposal, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Feedback, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1989 June-1989 August (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1989 April-1989 May (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1989 January-1989 March (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1988 November-1988 December (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1988 September-1988 October (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1988 June-1988 August (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - correspondence, 1988 January-1988 May (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1987 September-1987 December (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1987 June -1987 August (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1987 January-1987 May (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - correspondence, 1986 November-1986 December (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1986 September-1986 October (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - China Institute, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Campus photo slides, ca. 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Symposium Southern Italy and America, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Southern Italy and America Symposium Planning, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Southern Italy and America Symposium Planning, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - CAS Minutes and Memos, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CAS Minutes and Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - CAS Minutes and Memos, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Council, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Council of Humanities, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Humanities Governance Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Research Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Research Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Research Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - China Institute, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Tai-Jai Music Cassette, ca. 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - China Institute VHS Tape, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Three Year Plan Update, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Three Year Plan Update, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Three Year Plan Update, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Three Year Plan Update, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Three Year Plan Update, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Five Year Plan Update, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Five Year Plan Update, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Three Year Plan, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Five year plan, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Planning Memorandum, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Five Year Update, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Five Year Plan Update, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Five Year Plan, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Five Year, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Five Year, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Five Year, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Five Year, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Iris Newsletter, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Cornel West, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Report on Schweitzer Chair Research, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - College Personnel Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Search Director for International, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - China Institute Brochure, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Global Education Summer, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Search Committee Human Diversity, 1989 October 31-1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bibliographies, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Dissemination Activities, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Dissemination Reports, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Dissemination Reports, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Dissemination Reports, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Dissemination Reports, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Dissemination Reports, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Dissemination Reports, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Capital District Humanities Program, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - CDHP Executive Committee, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Committee Minutes, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Press Kit, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Council, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Council, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Council Minutes, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Five Year Plan, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Committee Questionnaires, 1985 June (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Tropical Agenda, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Ideas Committee, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - History Culture Committees, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Black History Programs, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Program Original Proposals, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Publicity Press Records, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Publicity Brochure, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Organization Descriptions, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Project Proposal, ca. 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Toni Morrison Project, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Schweitzer Chair Proposal, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Brochures, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Continuation Proposal, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Program, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - By Laws, ca. 1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Personnel, 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Foreign Languages Future Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Foreign Languages Future Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Foreign Languages Future Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - College Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - College Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - College Calendar, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - College Calendar, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - College Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Audio Visual Materials in Instruction, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Review Committee, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Music Studio at Suny Albany, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Beethoven Festival Program, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Undergraduate Journal, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Chataqua Program, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Philosophies, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Budget Request, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Brochure, ca. 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Youth Theatre, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Theatre Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Institute Files, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Transition Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Summer Sessions, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Summer Sessions, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Summer Sessions Mats, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Summer Sessions, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Summer Sessions, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Summer Sessions, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Applications, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Applications, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Applications, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate Achievement Celebration, 1991 April 16 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate Achievement Celebration, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Undergraduate Achievement Celebration, 1989 April 12 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Undergraduate Achievement Celebration, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Undergraduate Achievement Celebration, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Undergraduate Achievement Celebration, 1987 March (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - College Council, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - College Council, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - College Council, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - College Council, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - College Council, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - College Council, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - College Council, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - College Council, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - College Council, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Review Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bain Acting, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Center for the arts and humanities, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Research Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Research Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Research Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Budget Requests, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Discretionary Increases, 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Discretionary Increases, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Space Inventory, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Budget Request, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Music, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Music L Ensemble Proposal, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Linguistics MA Proposals, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Committee for Proposed Department of Linguistics, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Cognitive Science, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Program Merger, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Arts Education, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Art Education, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - For Judaic Studies, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - English Consultants, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - English, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - English Graduate Program Consultant, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Program in Humanistic Studies, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Classics, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Francine Frank Dean, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Center for the Arts Humanities, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Center for the Arts Humanities, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Center for the Arts Humanities, 1986 May (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Dean, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Deans File, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Art Gallery, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Records and Policies, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Program Review, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Exchange Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Namkai Delegation, 1982 April 29-1982 May 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Nanjing University Visit, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Studies Director, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Studies, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Pac, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Performing Arts Center, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Pac, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Performing Arts Center, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Assistant Director, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - NYC State Writers Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - NYC State Writers Institute, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Writers Institute, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Theatre Institute, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Theatre Institute, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Theatre Institute, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Theatre Institute, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Theatre Institute, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Theatre Institute Personnel, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Theatre Institute, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Theatre Institute, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Theatre Institute, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Theatre Institute, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Pac Coordinating Committee, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pac, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Department of Philosophy Proposal, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)